{
    "QuizID": "S1",
    "QuizContent": [
        {
            "QuestionID": "1",
            "Question": "In which year did the ABAP programming language turn 40?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "2020",
                "B": "2021",
                "C": "2022",
                "D": "2023"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "D",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "2",
            "Question": "What is the transaction code for the Screen Painter in the ABAP Workbench?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "SE31",
                "B": "SE80",
                "C": "SE51",
                "D": "SE38"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "C",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "3",
            "Question": "When was object-oriented programming (ABAP Objects) introduced into the ABAP Application Server?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "In the 1990s",
                "B": "In the 2000s",
                "C": "In the 1980s",
                "D": "ABAP Objects?"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "A",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "4",
            "Question": "In which year was SAP BTP, ABAP environment launched?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "2017",
                "B": "2018",
                "C": "2020",
                "D": "2021"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "5",
            "Question": "What paradigm shift has SAP HANA initiated as the underlying database in ABAP programming?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Data-to-UI",
                "B": "Data-to-Code",
                "C": "Code-to-Data",
                "D": "UI-to-Code"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "C",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "6",
            "Question": "With which AS ABAP release was CDS and AMDP introduced?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "7.40",
                "B": "7.31",
                "C": "7.50",
                "D": "7.02"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "A",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "7",
            "Question": "How many secondary keys can an internal table have in ABAP?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "Keine",
                "B": "5",
                "C": "10",
                "D": "15"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "D",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "8",
            "Question": "Which isolation techniques are part of ABAP unit testing?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "eCATT and Test Double Frameworks ",
                "B": "Smoke Seams and Test Double Frameworks",
                "C": "ABAP Unit Runner and Test Double Frameworks",
                "D": "Test Seams and Test Double Frameworks"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "D",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "9",
            "Question": "How many classes are currently released in the cloud base?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "approx. 2000",
                "B": "approx. 1000",
                "C": "approx. 500",
                "D": "approx. 250"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "B",
            "Explanation": ""
        },
        {
            "QuestionID": "10",
            "Question": "How many keywords are there in ABAP?",
            "Content": [],
            "Answers": {
                "A": "522",
                "B": "937",
                "C": "1024",
                "D": "1250"
            },
            "RightAnswer": "D",
            "Explanation": "ABAP is the programming language with the most keywords, especially historically."
        }  
    ]
}